# **HIDEAKI MYAMURA**

# Senior Fullstack Developer

📞 +447470723109 🍳 Dreamfullstacker@gmail.com 🕜 http://dream.fullstacker.com

▼ Tokyo, Japan

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

01/2017 - 07/2019

Rikkeisoft

Osaka

Rikkeisoft has delivered 1000+ projects, many with big Japanese corporations. Average customer satisfaction rate of Rikkeisoft is 90%, largely due to our thorough quality assurance and testing at every stage and prior to final project delivery.

- Leading a small team on a variety of development projects and delivering solutions to meet and exceed client's briefs
- Responsive design
- Version control systems

#### SENIOR Blockchain DEVELOPER

10/2019 - 12/2021

**METHOD IT** 

METHOD IT offers IT services and solutions to companies in Tokyo. METHOD IT do this because we have a passion for the latest business technologies and service with a personal touch.

- Worked alongside the senior web developers to deliver optimum performance of client's websites.
- **Build smart contract**
- Deploy and test
- Continuous integration

### **EDUCATION**

**High School Diploma** 

09/2009 - 09/2013

### Waseda University Senior High School

Computer Science

10/2013 - 04/2017

#### Waseda University

#### SUMMARY

If given a choice, my desired job title would be that of lead senior full stack engineer. My seven years of experience in web, app development plus my education in professional and technical writing make me an ideal candidate for this position and have additionally prepared me to take on more leadership-oriented roles such as full stack engineer

I like to be in the back and front of tech hence my passion for web and blockchain development.

I put my heart and soul into every project I work on, going non-stop till it is brought to perfection.

My strongest attribute is my determination. I take on every challenge head-on and do what I need to accomplish my goals, even when the challenge is difficult My unique attribute is passion. I think without a passion for what you are doing, it is not possible to ideally perform your job.

Just thinking of programming as my hobby, I started my career for software development in the companies when I was studying at the Waseda University. This was an amazing experience for me to grow as an IT technician. I will never give up on my way. Thanks for reading!



#### **SKILLS**

Blockchain · Cryptocurrency · NFT ·

Solidity · Codeigniter · Laravel ·

Node.js · Express · MongoDB ·

MySQL · React.js · Next.js · Vue.js ·

Nuxt.js · Vue storefront · Angular.js ·

Nest.js · Svelte · Bootstrap ·

TailwindCSS · GateBy · jQuery ·

Shopify · Amazon Web Service ·

React Native · Flutter

LAMP · MERN · MEVN · MEAN ·

Working with command lines ·

Version control systems ·

DevOps practices ·

Front-end systems · Debugging

#### STRENGTHS

Sociability

Client's satisfaction

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

T'm graduated Waseda university

> A Progressive University Of **Traditions**

Waseda's culture and traditions have evolved over time since 1882, but its founding principles remain firm. The Waseda spirit lives in the hearts of over 600.000 alumni.

#### LANGUAGES

Japanese Native **English Proficient** 

0

## **PASSIONS**

Golf, Reading, Travel

